
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729292554553}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729292555648}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729292556324}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729292557073}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Peter owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "Ivan is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729292557720}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does Elena own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729292558351}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Peter is at house 2.", "Peter is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a zebra.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "Peter lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "Elena owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729292558936}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Peter is at house 3."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729292559760}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Theodora", "Peter"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729292560610}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes.", "Peter is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729292561685}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Theodora, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does Elena own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729292652486}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a cat.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729292653095}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729292653762}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729292654410}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a cat.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729292655115}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729292655745}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena is at house 2.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729292656438}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729292657013}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "Peter is in red clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in blue clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729292657661}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 4 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729292658376}
